minekey.com 2010-09-27

# Privacy : Minekey

| 

Effective July 31st, 2008

By using the Minekey Application or Site you are consenting to our Processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information all of which will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the U.S., your personally identifiable information will be transferred to the U.S. and processed and stored there under U.S. privacy standards. By visiting our Application or Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to and processing in the U.S. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [privacy@minekey.com](mailto:privacy@minekey.com). 

#### Information Collection and Use

The Site may require some amount of personal information to maintain account information and communicate with users who have registered with Minekey. We also collect personally identifiable information to provide you with the Minekey service made available through the Site and Application, to communicate with you, and to manage your user account through which you can take advantage of the services made available through the Site, which include, without limitation, browsing the Site and Application and using the Service. If additional information is needed, we will amend this policy and post the changes on the Site. We may also notify you via email of the changes although we will use good sense and reasonable judgment when doing so. When you visit the Site or Application, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. Except in the instances described herein, we do not use this information to identify you personally. We use it to monitor use of the Site and the Minekey Service and for the Site's technical administration. 

#### Cookies

are removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Information Sharing and Disclosure the system information stores or who have a reasonable need to come in contact with and make use of such information for account purposes. Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement. Minekey cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Minekey or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law. Business Transfers. If any or all of the assets of Minekey are acquired by, or if Minekey is acquired by or merged with another entity, we may share some or all of your information with this entity. Use of Aggregated Information. We may disclose aggregated information about the use of the Minekey application or Site to business partners, prospective investors, and others. Additionally, we may produce industry-standard traffic reports for assessing use of the Minekey Site or Application. We will use information only in the aggregate in order to monitor and improve Minekey. 

#### Security

Minekey is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ industry standard administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. However, no Internet site can fully eliminate security risks. We will disclose any compromise of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

#### Links to Other Sites

The Minekey Application or Site may contain links to other websites. The fact that Minekey links to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect from you through this Site. Other sites, including other websites that may use Minekey services, follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

|   
---|---  
|   quick links  
---
